Tell-Tale is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Michael Cuesta.
A man's recently transplanted heart leads him on a frantic search to
find the donor's killer before a similar fate befalls him.
Terry, played by Josh Lucas.
Elizabeth, played by Lena Headey.
Van Doren, played by Brian Cox.
Angela, played by Bea Miller.
The Surgeon, played by Dallas Roberts.
Lethe, played by Ulrich Thomsen.
Tell-Tale is a 2009 science fiction horror film inspired by Edgar
Allan Poe's 1843 short story "The Tell-Tale Heart".
It is directed by Michael Cuesta and stars Josh Lucas, Lena Headey, and
Brian Cox and is produced by Tony Scott and Ridley Scott.
A man's recently transplanted heart leads him on a frantic search to
find the donor's killer before a similar fate befalls him.
The film explores themes of heart attack,
detective, paranoia, flashback, murder.
The tone is dark and intense and emotional.